The Classic Continues
Return to Never Land is a adventure, fantasy,
animation film directed by Robin Budd.
In 1940, the world is besieged by World War II.
Wendy, all grown up, has two children; including Jane, who does
not believe Wendy's stories about Peter Pan.
Jane / Young Wendy (Voice), played by Harriet Owen.
Peter Pan (Voice), played by Blayne Weaver.
Smee / Pirates (Voice), played by Jeff Bennett.
Wendy Darling (voice), played by Kath Soucie.
Captain Hook (voice), played by Corey Burton.
Danny (voice), played by Andrew McDonough.
Return to Never Land (also known as Peter Pan in Return to Never Land) is a 2002 American
animated adventure fantasy film produced by Walt Disney Television Animation.
A sequel to Walt Disney Feature Animation's 1953 film Peter Pan, the
film is based on the 1908 play When Wendy Grew Up by J.M.
It follows Wendy's daughter, Jane, who is mistakenly abducted and brought to
Neverland and must learn to believe in order to return home.
The film stars the voices of Harriet Owen, Blayne Weaver, Corey Burton, Jeff
Bennett, Kath Soucie, Spencer Breslin, and Bradley Pierce.
Return to Never Land premiered at the El Capitan Theatre in Los Angeles, California on February 10, 2002,
and was released in the United States in February 15, by Buena Vista Pictures Distribution.
Despite receiving mixed reviews from critics, it was a box-office success like its
predecessor, grossing $115 million against a $20 million budget.
The film explores themes of flying, cartoon, sequel.